afterschoolafrica.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | After School Africa

**Privacy Policy for AfterSchoolAfrica.com**

##  **Short Version**

This site keeps all your personal information secret. Your personal information is not shared with anyone else.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@afterschoolafrica.com

##  **Long Version**

This privacy statement has been created in order to demonstrate the firm commitment of [www.afterschoolafrica.com](https://www.afterschoolafrica.com/about/contact/) to privacy. The following statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.afterschoolafrica.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.afterschoolafrica.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.afterschoolafrica.com use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.afterschoolafrica.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.afterschoolafrica.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display advertisements and links that appear on www.afterschoolafrica.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.afterschoolafrica.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.afterschoolafrica.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Google Analytics**

This website uses Google analytics to track the visitors’ geographical location, device being used to access the website, public links being accessed by the user, time duration being spent on the website just with the intentions to provide better performance, content and user experience to the visitors.

 **Order and Purchase**

If you are making order to purchase any product or service from us, any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone.

 **Email and RSS Subscription**

This site allows visitors to sign up for a free updates by providing an email address. The email address you provide is used only to send you the free information, and you can unsubscribe by clicking a link in any issue of the update.

 **About our Content**

The content on this site is copyrighted by AfterSchoolAfrica and any author or user or any 3rd party does not have any right over the same. While most of the programs we publish are openly available online, the content is purely the output of our research team, our content sharing network and the contribution from our members.

We encourage our members to use our content to share and promote opportunities and possibilities in education and development to increase the knowledge.

The content must not be used for 3rd party commercial purpose by any other party except for AfterSchoolAfrica or by a person/organization authorized by AfterSchoolAfrica in writing.

The content doesn’t support any individual or any organization or any product of any other party. The content is not intended to hurt any individuals’, groups’, organizations’ nor anybody’s moral, religious or ethical beliefs.

 **External Links**

www.afterschoolafrica.com contains links to other sites. www.afterschoolafrica.com and its owner are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Users are advised to verify third party sites linked here for clarification.
